//   ---------------------------------------subraction questions--------------------------
const level1SubQuestions = [
    {
        "question": "What is 43 - 1?",
        "options": ["42", "44", "41", "45"],
        "answer": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 87 - 1?",
        "options": ["86", "88", "85", "89"],
        "answer": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 12 - 1?",
        "options": ["11", "13", "10", "14"],
        "answer": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 55 - 1?",
        "options": ["54", "56", "53", "57"],
        "answer": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 76 - 1?",
        "options": ["75", "77", "74", "78"],
        "answer": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 23 - 1?",
        "options": ["22", "24", "21", "25"],
        "answer": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 98 - 1?",
        "options": ["97", "99", "96", "100"],
        "answer": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 34 - 1?",
        "options": ["33", "35", "32", "36"],
        "answer": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 67 - 1?",
        "options": ["66", "68", "65", "69"],
        "answer": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 5 - 1?",
        "options": ["4", "6", "3", "7"],
        "answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 91 - 1?",
        "options": ["90", "92", "89", "93"],
        "answer": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 20 - 1?",
        "options": ["19", "21", "18", "22"],
        "answer": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 68 - 1?",
        "options": ["67", "69", "66", "70"],
        "answer": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 3 - 1?",
        "options": ["2", "4", "1", "5"],
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 49 - 1?",
        "options": ["48", "50", "47", "51"],
        "answer": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 82 - 1?",
        "options": ["81", "83", "80", "84"],
        "answer": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 37 - 1?",
        "options": ["36", "38", "35", "39"],
        "answer": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 71 - 1?",
        "options": ["70", "72", "69", "73"],
        "answer": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 15 - 1?",
        "options": ["14", "16", "13", "17"],
        "answer": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 64 - 1?",
        "options": ["63", "65", "62", "66"],
        "answer": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 8 - 1?",
        "options": ["7", "9", "6", "10"],
        "answer": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 53 - 1?",
        "options": ["52", "54", "51", "55"],
        "answer": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 97 - 1?",
        "options": ["96", "98", "95", "99"],
        "answer": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 29 - 1?",
        "options": ["28", "30", "27", "31"],
        "answer": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 46 - 1?",
        "options": ["45", "47", "44", "48"],
        "answer": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 89 - 1?",
        "options": ["88", "90", "87", "91"],
        "answer": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 41 - 1?",
        "options": ["40", "42", "39", "43"],
        "answer": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 74 - 1?",
        "options": ["73", "75", "72", "76"],
        "answer": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 19 - 1?",
        "options": ["18", "20", "17", "21"],
        "answer": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 61 - 1?",
        "options": ["60", "62", "59", "63"],
        "answer": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 7 - 1?",
        "options": ["6", "8", "5", "9"],
        "answer": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 94 - 1?",
        "options": ["93", "95", "92", "96"],
        "answer": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 58 - 1?",
        "options": ["57", "59", "56", "60"],
        "answer": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 26 - 1?",
        "options": ["25", "27", "24", "28"],
        "answer": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 70 - 1?",
        "options": ["69", "71", "68", "72"],
        "answer": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 13 - 1?",
        "options": ["12", "14", "11", "15"],
        "answer": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 85 - 1?",
        "options": ["84", "86", "83", "87"],
        "answer": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 32 - 1?",
        "options": ["31", "33", "30", "34"],
        "answer": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 79 - 1?",
        "options": ["78", "80", "77", "81"],
        "answer": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 1 - 1?",
        "options": ["0", "2", "-1", "1"],
        "answer": "0"
    },
    {
        "question": " What is 52 - 1?",
        "options": ["51", "53", "50", "54"],
        "answer": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 95 - 1?",
        "options": ["94", "96", "93", "97"],
        "answer": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 40 - 1?",
        "options": ["39", "41", "38", "42"],
        "answer": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 73 - 1?",
        "options": ["72", "74", "71", "75"],
        "answer": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 17 - 1?",
        "options": ["16", "18", "15", "19"],
        "answer": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 59 - 1?",
        "options": ["58", "60", "57", "61"],
        "answer": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 4 - 1?",
        "options": ["3", "5", "2", "6"],
        "answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 88 - 1?",
        "options": ["87", "89", "86", "90"],
        "answer": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 31 - 1?",
        "options": ["30", "32", "29", "33"],
        "answer": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 66 - 1?",
        "options": ["65", "67", "64", "68"],
        "answer": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 22 - 1?",
        "options": ["21", "23", "20", "24"],
        "answer": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 65 - 1?",
        "options": ["64", "66", "63", "67"],
        "answer": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 10 - 1?",
        "options": ["9", "11", "8", "12"],
        "answer": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 50 - 1?",
        "options": ["49", "51", "48", "52"],
        "answer": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 83 - 1?",
        "options": ["82", "84", "81", "85"],
        "answer": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 28 - 1?",
        "options": ["27", "29", "26", "30"],
        "answer": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 62 - 1?",
        "options": ["61", "63", "60", "64"],
        "answer": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 2 - 1?",
        "options": ["1", "3", "0", "4"],
        "answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 47 - 1?",
        "options": ["46", "48", "45", "49"],
        "answer": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 81 - 1?",
        "options": ["80", "82", "79", "83"],
        "answer": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 35 - 1?",
        "options": ["34", "36", "33", "37"],
        "answer": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 78 - 1?",
        "options": ["77", "79", "76", "80"],
        "answer": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 14 - 1?",
        "options": ["13", "15", "12", "16"],
        "answer": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 56 - 1?",
        "options": ["55", "57", "54", "58"],
        "answer": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 25 - 1?",
        "options": ["24", "26", "23", "27"],
        "answer": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 60 - 1?",
        "options": ["59", "61", "58", "62"],
        "answer": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 9 - 1?",
        "options": ["8", "10", "7", "11"],
        "answer": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 54 - 1?",
        "options": ["53", "55", "52", "56"],
        "answer": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 80 - 1?",
        "options": ["79", "81", "78", "82"],
        "answer": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 38 - 1?",
        "options": ["37", "39", "36", "40"],
        "answer": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 92 - 1?",
        "options": ["91", "93", "90", "94"],
        "answer": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 16 - 1?",
        "options": ["15", "17", "14", "18"],
        "answer": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 48 - 1?",
        "options": ["47", "49", "46", "50"],
        "answer": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 86 - 1?",
        "options": ["85", "87", "84", "88"],
        "answer": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 30 - 1?",
        "options": ["29", "31", "28", "32"],
        "answer": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 75 - 1?",
        "options": ["74", "76", "73", "77"],
        "answer": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 21 - 1?",
        "options": ["20", "22", "19", "23"],
        "answer": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 57 - 1?",
        "options": ["56", "58", "55", "59"],
        "answer": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 93 - 1?",
        "options": ["92", "94", "91", "95"],
        "answer": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 6 - 1?",
        "options": ["5", "7", "4", "8"],
        "answer": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 45 - 1?",
        "options": ["44", " 46", "43", "47"],
        "answer": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 84 - 1?",
        "options": ["83", "85", "82", "86"],
        "answer": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 36 - 1?",
        "options": ["35", "37", "34", "38"],
        "answer": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 69 - 1?",
        "options": ["68", "70", "67", "71"],
        "answer": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 27 - 1?",
        "options": ["26", "28", "25", "29"],
        "answer": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 63 - 1?",
        "options": ["62", "64", "61", "65"],
        "answer": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 11 - 1?",
        "options": ["10", "12", "9", "13"],
        "answer": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 51 - 1?",
        "options": ["50", "52", "49", "53"],
        "answer": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 90 - 1?",
        "options": ["89", "91", "88", "92"],
        "answer": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 24 - 1?",
        "options": ["23", "25", "22", "26"],
        "answer": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 72 - 1?",
        "options": ["71", "73", "70", "74"],
        "answer": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 18 - 1?",
        "options": ["17", "19", "16", "20"],
        "answer": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 42 - 1?",
        "options": ["41", "43", "40", "44"],
        "answer": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 77 - 1?",
        "options": ["76", "78", "75", "79"],
        "answer": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 33 - 1?",
        "options": ["32", "34", "31", "35"],
        "answer": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 99 - 1?",
        "options": ["98", "100", "97", "101"],
        "answer": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 39 - 1?",
        "options": ["38", "40", "37", "41"],
        "answer": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 58 - 1?",
        "options": ["57", "59", "56", "60"],
        "answer": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 96 - 1?",
        "options": ["95", "97", "94", "98"],
        "answer": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 0 - 1?",
        "options": ["-1", "1", "-2", "0"],
        "answer": "-1"
    }
      
    
  ];
  function shuffleArray(array) {
    for (let i = array.length - 1; i > 0; i--) {
      const j = Math.floor(Math.random() * (i + 1));
      [array[i], array[j]] = [array[j], array[i]];
    }
    return array;
  }
  
  level1SubQuestions.forEach(question => {
    question.options = shuffleArray(question.options);
  });

export default level1SubQuestions;